Uh, I I got two for you. First one's a
pretty quick one. Are you prepared to be
talking about yourself as much as you
will from now on to the summer?
>> No, hopefully hopefully that's what this
is for. So then you guys can you guys
can do it for me. So um but it's there's
a lot of stuff coming up that's that's
very exciting. I think the talking
aspect of it. Um
the big thing is the speech up there in
August. That's the one thing that I got
to really get figured out. But, uh,
hopefully hopefully everybody else can
do can do all the talk and I can just
sit here and answer you guys questions.
>> Yeah. Um, that's what I figured you'd
say. Uh, I I wanted to ask about this. U
was it, you spent your entire career in
Carolina. You'll be the first person um
to do that who has made the Pro Football
Hall of Fame because obviously Julius
Pepper spent some time in other places.
Does that make it much How much more
special does it make it the fact that
you stayed um with the Panthers your
entire um career?
>> I think you know you look at you look at
Pep and his career
>> was substantially twice as long as mine.
So I think that has something to do with
it as well. But I think playing in
Carolina couldn't have been I couldn't
have been in a better situation from the
people that were there, the city that
was there, the guys that were on the
team. I think I was very much a product
of the people and the system in Carolina
and I think I was just very fortunate to
be here the whole time. I loved it. I
love the guys. I love the city. I love
the organization. Um, so to me, I think
it's it's super cool. You don't you
don't have the opportunity in the NFL to
play for the same team your whole
career. And for me to have the
opportunity to play in Carolina with
such a great group of people um was
really special.
>> Great. Thanks, man.
>> Hey, little Chris Jenkins,
congratulations, sir.
>> Thank you.
>> Hey, a little bit building off what Alex
just spoke about. You know, been your
whole career here in Carolina and then
since your career, you've still been
very much in planning here at the
organization and with the city. Can you
elaborate just a little bit on what pull
this organization has and this city has
on you that makes it special for you?
>> Yeah, I I love the organization, the
people. I've got so many great friends
that I made in the organization and you
know I got here I turned 21 a week
before the draft. So when I got down
here I was a I was a kid trying to
figure everything out and I think for me
there was a lot of younger people in the
organization when I when I got in. I
mean, Ryan Anderson was, you guys all
know Ryan. Ryan's a couple years older
than I am, and he was my point guy with
all of you. And it was just, I was so
lucky to have a guy that was around my
age. I was going through a lot of the
same stuff. And Mike Anderson, his
brother, was the same way. Greg Almond
was one of our equipment guys that is
still one of my really good friends to
this day. I think
that was a big important factor to me I
think early on was there was younger
people in the building that were just
good dudes. You know that obviously all
the players I talk about Greg and Thomas
and Ryan and all those guys a lot but I
think the people pulled me in and kept
me pulled in and I just I love the city.
There's a lot to do. The people that I'm
closest with still live in Charlotte. I
think there's plenty of opportunities
with for me outside of football. And
then like you said I love the team. my
love of the organization. I've had so
much fun being around it. You know, I
did the scouting for a year. That was
super fun. And then the radio broadcast
with with Jake and Anishh and and
Langden and those guys and Baloni and we
have such a and our our squad is so fun.
I have such a great time with it and I
see no reason to leave. And also Sharon
Thors on her her and KB split the the
sideline duty. So I love the city. I
love the organization. A lot of my best
friends still live in Charlotte and for
me it just makes the most sense.
>> And just a quick followup with that is
with you being in radio, we get to see
you around a lot now and I've seen you
countless places and every time I see
you, you're recognized and and people
speak to you and no matter the
circumstance and I've seen you in so
many different places, uh you're still a
very gracious and kind person during
those times. What how did how did that
come about within you or who influenced
that kind of personality within you?
>> I think my parents. I mean, you grow up
at such from such a young age or being
around two great people that set the
tone for your life. You know, my parents
were fantastic. They they led by example
and they and what they said they did.
So, hey, be nice to people. That's all
they ever did. Smile at people. That's
what they did. You treat people how you
want to be treated. That's all they ever
did. And it wasn't the rules in our
house growing up weren't super
complicated. Um
it was just be be a good person. And it
might seem like the hard thing to do in
the moment, but in the long term it
usually always pays off for you. And um
I just think it's easier to be nice. I
don't I don't know. I feel like it's not
that that difficult. And then I mean
let's just Chris, let's be honest, man.
Anytime I see people in the facility
before the games, everyone wants to talk
about football and I like talking about
football. So, I feel like we're all kind
of there for the same reason. Thank you
so much.
>> We'll go with Bill Oren followed by
Bashtai Hurt.
>> Hey Luke, congratulations. I I'll echo
everybody's congratulations from here on
out. Um I'm just curious sort of
piggybacking on Alex's point. How how
comfortable are you sort of facing your
legacy in the game of football? Because
it's never really something you've been
comfortable talking about and it feels
like now is kind of a good opportunity
to do that.
>> Yeah. Honestly,
since he asked that question, I've been
kind of thinking about it a little bit.
And I think the further away I've gotten
from I don't I guess that was was that
last week or two weeks ago, whatever
Super Bowl was, the cooler it's starting
to kind of settle in. And um I think I
always talk about like Drew for example,
I always talk about how normal it was to
play. Oh, we're playing the Saints and
Drew Brees again. And as you get further
away from the game, you realize how
special it is to have the opportunity to
have played against Drew as much as as
we did when we were in Carolina. And you
know, dating back to when I was a rookie
down in New Orleans, that first that
Hall of Fame class walked out. I was at
honor as a Hall of Fame class walked out
on the stage and you're like, man, that
would be so cool to be up there. Look at
those dude. Those are all the guys that
I watched growing up. and how special it
is when the older guys walk up with
their jackets on and you know welcome
all welcome them all in. And then, you
know, when I was growing up, it was
still the knock on the door and the
hotel room way back in the day. And then
I remember watching Pep's when they came
and knocked on his door. And then you
kind of then you you know, you think
about it and then Pep was standing in my
my family room a couple weeks ago and
it's starting to settle in like this is